Narrator: 1
Speaker: A wind-up torch.
This torch works using a dynamo. The battery is recharged by winding the handle.
It’s perfect for emergencies, or in places where there is no electricity.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: A shoe that grows.
In many places, parents can’t afford to buy new shoes when their children’s feet grow.
This comfortable, long-lasting shoe is completely adjustable, and can expand up to five sizes.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: A solar hearing aid. Over 600 million people need hearing aids,
but at least half can’t afford to buy them, or to replace the batteries.
This cost-effective,
eco-friendly device has a rechargeable battery which lasts for two to three years.